

MARVIN ROSETE

Web Graphic Designer

About Me

Web Graphic Designer with 5 years experience creating, maintaining functional, attractive and responsive website for business or marketing campaign using cms



0997 601 3084



Maben1120@gmail.com



Fourth Estate Subd., Barangay San Antonio, Sucat Parañaque City 1715

SKILLS

WEB DEVELOPMENT TOOLS







October CMS

Wordpress

WIX

DESIGN TOOLS

Illustrator







Affer Effects

Photoshop



Canva

EXPERIENCE

EnfraUSA Solutions Inc WEB AND GRAPHIC DESIGNER 2020 - 2022

- Building and maintaining websites using October CMS.
- Doing Quality Assurance to all websites my team created
- Design online collaterals
- · Managing the client requirements and communicating them effectively to our on-shore team.

Thrive Web Media **UI/UX DESINGER**

2023 - Present (Part-time)

- Create Branding/Logo
- Create wireframes and interactive prototypes to visualize and communicate design ideas effectively.
- Design online collaterals
- Motion Graphics

EDUCATION

Premiere Computer Learning Center

Information Communication Technology 2014 - 2016

Vocational

United Christian Academy

Computer Hardware Servicing NCII

Premiere Computer Learning Center Computer Hardware Servicing NCIII

REFERENCES

JUNIUS REYES

Product Specialist ConvertKit 09063915150

Aaron Nikko Gonzales

Web & Graphic Designer Sourcefit 09087832399